Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 3 and District 3 Locals, 1936-1990s UE.4.1.3
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 3 Locals, 2.
  - Local 509
    - Local 509 Correspondence, Minutes, Questionnaire and Wage Rates, March 17, 1938-December 12, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 32)
      - Harley to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, December 12, 1947; 11.
      - Health Questionnaire, 12.
      - Stromberg Carlson Wage Rates, 13.
      - Harley to Dave Regarding Finances, 14.
      - Wofford to LaPine Regarding Otto Benz and National Labor Relations Board, 15.
    - Local 509 Leaflets (Box 7, Folder 33)
      - Statement of Local 509 Regarding Stromberg Carlson Company, 1.
    - Local 509 Press Release, July 1941 (Box 7, Folder 34)
      - Press Release Regarding Strikes, Conscription, Political Action and National Defense Mediation Board, July 1941; 1.
  - Local 1581
    - Local 1581 Officers Lists, December 1946-June 1949 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Local 1581 Officers Lists, October 18, 1949-August 29, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Local 1581 Officer Minutes, November 1, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Local 1581 Incoming Correspondence, February 19, 1947-September 3, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 38)
      - William Cahn to Tobie Wallis Regarding Publications, April 14, 1947; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to C. H. Van Tyne Regarding Veterans and Dues, Februray 19, 1947; 2.
      - Emspak to Louis LaRovette Regarding Local 424 United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, June 3, 1947; 3.
      - Emspak to George Gould Regarding Finances, November 28, 1947; 4.
      - Emspak to Willaim Evans Regarding Finances, September 15, 1948; 5.
      - Emspak to Dorothy Wynne Regarding Finances, October 1, 1948; 6.
      - Emspak to Wynne Regarding Dues Check-off, October 20, 1948; 7.
      - Emspak to Wynne Regarding Finances, November 10-23, 1948; 8-9.
      - Emspak to Wynne Regarding United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, November 29, 1948; 10.
      - Emspak to Evans Regarding Finances, January 5, 1949; 11.
      - Emspak to Charles Wise Regarding Finances, March 11, 1949; 12.
      - Emspak to Loretta Kaczynska Regarding Local 1581 Officers, June 21, 1949; 13.
      - Emspak to Theodore Wierzbic Regarding Finances, July 1, 1949; 14.
      - Emspak to Wierzbic Regarding Finances and Factionalism, August 15, 1949; 15.
      - Michael Jimenez to Wierzbic Regarding Wages and Finances, September 3, 1949; 16.
      - Russ Nixon to Leo Skowronski Regarding Political Action Committee, November 3, 1947; 17.
      - David Ratner Telegram to Gould, November 4,1947; 18.
      - Ratner to Wierzbic Regarding Finances, July 7, 1947; 19.
    - Local 1581 Outgoing Correspondence, June 24, 1947-November 2, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 39)
      - George Gould Telegram to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Taft-Hartley, General Strike and Congress of Industrial Organizations, June 24, 1947; 1.
      - Gould to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances and Local 1581 Headquarters, October 16, 1947; 2.
      - Gould to David Ratner Regarding Finances, October 28, 1947; 3.
      - Gould to Emspak Regarding Finances and Local 1581 Headquarters, November 10, 1947; 4.
      - Gould to Ratner Regarding Local 1581 Officer Elections and Finances, May 13, 1948; 5.
      - Lillian Grant to Janet Barish Regarding Supplies, July 21, 1949; 6.
      - Charles Jeske to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, October 14, 1947; 7.
      - Louis LaRouette to Emspak Regarding Local 424 United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry and Congress of Industrial Organization, May 27, 1947; 8.
      - Leo Skowronski to Ratner Regarding Finances, April 18, 1947; 9.
      - Skowronski to Emspak Regarding Finances, June 25, 1947; 10.
      - Skowronski to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, October 8, 1947; 11.
      - Tobie Wallis to Emspak Regarding Publicaitons, March 9, 1947; 12.
      - Theodore Wierzbic to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 25, 1948; 13.
      - Wierzbic to Ratner Regarding Finances, May 17, 1949; 14.
      - Wierzbic to Emspak Regarding Finances, May 27, 1949; 15.
      - Wierzbic to Ratner Regarding Finances, July 5, 1949; 16.
      - Wierzbic to Emspak Regarding Local 1581 Suspensions and Factionalism, August 12, 1949; 17.
      - Wierzbic Telegram to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism, Inter-union Rivalry and Congress of Industrial Organizations, November 2, 1949; 18.
    - Local 1581 Outgoing Correspondence, September 27, 1948-May 8, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 40)
      - Charles Wise to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, May 8, 1949; 1.
      - Dorothy Wynne to Emspak Regarding Supplies, September 27, 1948; 2.
      - Wynne to Emspak Regarding Supplies, October 14, 1948; 3.
      - Wynne to Emspak Regarding Finances and Factionalism, October 9, 1948; 4.
      - Wynne to Emspak Regarding United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, Rem-Rand and Political Action, November 17, 1948; 5.
      - Wyne to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Gould Trial, November 19, 1948; 6.
    - Local 1581 Per Capita, January 3-August 31, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 41)
      - Per Capita, January 3, 1949; 1.
      - Per Capita with Dues Summary, January 3, 1949; 2.
      - Per Capita with Dues Summary, February 7, 1949; 3.
      - Per Capita with Dues Summary and Memo, March 9, 1949; 4.
      - Per Capita with Dues Summary, May 8, 1949; 5.
      - Per Capita with Dues Summary, May 8, 1949; 6.
      - Per Capita with Dues Summary, August 8, 1949; 7.
      - Per Capita, August 31, 1949; 8.
    - Local 1581 Ledgers, June 1, 1948-June 30, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 42)
      - Schedules, June 1, 1948-June 30, 1949; 1.
      - Ledgers, January 1948-June 1949; 2-3.
    - Local 1581 Audits, January 20, 1947-August 10, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Local 1581 Organization, September 25-December 5, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 44)
      - Charles Rivers to Julius Emspak, September 25, 1946; 1.
      - Emspak to Leo Jandreau, October 1, 1946; 2.
      - Emspak to Rivers, October 1, 1946; 3.
      - Emspak to Edward Landy, October 31, 1946; 4.
      - Landy to Emspak, December 5, 1946; 5.
    - Local 1581 Membership Drive and Officers Election, March 26-May 19, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 45)
      - Arnold Miller to Stewards, May 26, 1947; 1.
      - Attention Stewards, 2.
      - Joseph Infante to James Matles, May 13, 1947; 3.
      - Ballot, May 15, 1947; 4.
      - Infante to Matles, May 19, 1947; 5.
    - Local 1581 Finances and Factionalism, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 46)
      - David Ratner to William Evans with Budget, January 6, 1949; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Michael Jimenez, April 29, 1949; 2.
      - Emspak to Joseph Infante, June 1, 1949; 3.
      - Infante to Emspak, June 3, 1949; 4.
      - Local 1581 Notes, 1949; 5.
      - Memo, 1949; 6.
      - Committee Report on Local 1581 Convention Loan, 1949; 7.
      - Action of the General Executive Board, August 10, 1949; 8.
    - Local 1581 Correspondence, Card Filling Correspondence and Notification, June 25, 1947-April 13, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 47)
      - Bill Gandall to UE Regarding Publicity, June 25, 1947; 1.
      - Gandall to Dave, July-September 1947; 2-3.
      - Joseph Infante to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, October 16, 1947; 4.
      - Card Filling Procedures, 5.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, April 13, 1948; 6.
    - Local 1581 Union Member, May 14, 1947-May 27, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Local 1581 Leaflets, 1947-1951 (Box 7, Folder 49)
      - UE Starts Wage Negotiations, March 25, 1947; 1.
      - May Dance, 1947; 2.
      - This Concerns You Regarding Membership Meeting, 1947; 3.
      - A Big Event Regarding Mass Meeting and Political Action, 1947; 4.
      - Membership Meeting, 1947; 5-6.
      - Important Membership Meeting Regarding Local 1581 Officer Elections, 1947; 7.
      - Tony Marino for President, 1947; 8.
      - It's A Lie Regarding Local 1581 Officers Elections, 1947; 9.
      - Westinghouse Workers Don't Want "Tammany Hall" Unionism Regarding Local 1581 Officers Elections, 1947; 10.
      - UE Unity Means Victory Regarding Local 1581 Officers Elections, 1947; 11.
      - Vote For Yourself Today Regarding Local 1581 Officers, Elections, 1947; 12.
      - Defend Your Gains Regarding Local 1581 Officer Election, 1947; 13.
      - UE Unity Regarding 1581 Officer Elections, 1947; 14.
      - Forward with the UE-Unity Candidates Regarding Local 1581 Officers Elections, 1947; 15.
      - UE Unity Slate Gains Sweeping Support Regarding Local 1581 Officers Elections, 1947; 16.
      - Look at the Record Regarding Local 1581 Officers Elections, 1947; 17.
      - Here Are the Facts Regarding Local 1581 Officers Elections, 1947; 18.
      - Local Defends to Stay in UE, December 1, 1949; 19.
      - Pact Ratified Regarding IUE Westinghouse and Cheektowaga, December 18, 1951; 20.
    - Local 1581 Pamphlets, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 50)
      - For a Strong Union Program Regarding Local 1581 Officers Elections, 1947; 1.